[
  {
    "id": "259",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "S3",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which S3 service automatically checks the replication status of S3 objects across different regions, providing near real-time metrics as well as failure notifications?",
      "answers": [
        "Cross-Region Replication Monitor",
        "MFA Delete",
        "CloudTrail",
        "Bucket Policies",
        "S3 object-level logging"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Cross-Region Replication Monitor"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "260",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "S3",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "S3 Lifecycle Management can be used in conjunction with versioning?",
      "answers": [
        "true",
        "false"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["true"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "261",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "S3",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "S3 Lifecycle Management can be applied to current versions but not previous versions?",
      "answers": [
        "true",
        "false, it can be applied to both current versions and previous versions",
        "false, it cannot be applied to either"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["false, it can be applied to both current versions and previous versions"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "262",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "S3",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 4",
      "question": "With S3 Lifecycle Management rules you can do which of these?",
      "answers": [
        "Transition to the Standard Infrequent Access storage class",
        "Archive to the Glacier storage class",
        "Transition to the One Zone Infrequent Access storage class",
        "Transition to the Reduced Redundancy storage class",
        "Permanently delete"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Transition to the Standard Infrequent Access storage class", "Archive to the Glacier storage class", "Transition to the One Zone Infrequent Access storage class", "Permanently delete"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "263",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "S3",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "With S3 Lifecycle Management rules when you transition to the Standard Infrequent Access storage class the object must be _________?",
      "answers": [
        "at least 128kb in size and 30 days after creation date",
        "at least 64kb in size and 30 days after creation date",
        "30 days after creation date",
        "at least 128kb in size",
        "at least 128kb in size and 60 days after creation date"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["at least 128kb in size and 30 days after creation date"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "264",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "S3",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "With S3 Lifecycle Management rules when you transition to the Glacier storage class the object must be _________?",
      "answers": [
        "30 days after transitioning to the Infrequent Access storage class or 60 days after creation date",
        "60 days after transitioning to the Infrequent Access storage class or 90 days after creation date",
        "30 days after creation date",
        "at least 128kb in size",
        "at least 128kb in size and 60 days after creation date"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["30 days after transitioning to the Infrequent Access storage class or 60 days after creation date"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "265",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "CloudFront",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "________ is a system of distributed servers (network) that deliver webpages and other web content to a user based on the geographic locations of the user, the origin of the web page, and the content delivery server?",
      "answers": [
        "Content Delivery Network (CDN)",
        "CloudFront",
        "CloudTrail",
        "Route 53"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Content Delivery Network (CDN)"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "266",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "CloudFront",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "________ is a the location where content will be cached, which is separate to an AWS Region or AZ?",
      "answers": [
        "Content Delivery Network (CDN)",
        "Edge Location",
        "Origin",
        "Distribution"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Edge Location"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "267",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "CloudFront",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "________ is a the origin of all the files that the CDN will distribute?",
      "answers": [
        "Content Delivery Network (CDN)",
        "Edge Location",
        "Origin",
        "Distribution"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Origin"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "268",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "CloudFront",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 4",
      "question": "The origin of the files that the CDN will distribute can be which of these?",
      "answers": [
        "S3 Bucket",
        "EC2 Instance",
        "an ELB",
        "Route 53",
        "CloudTrail",
        "Auto-scaling Group"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["S3 Bucket", "EC2 Instance", "an ELB", "Route 53"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "269",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "CloudFront",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "________ is a the name given to the CDN which consists of a colection of Edge Locations?",
      "answers": [
        "Content Delivery Network (CDN)",
        "Edge Location",
        "Origin",
        "Distribution"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Distribution"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "270",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "CloudFront",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "With CloudFront, requests for your content are automatically routed to the ________, so content is delivered with the best possible performance?",
      "answers": [
        "nearest Edge Location",
        "an ELB",
        "an Auto-scaling Group",
        "a Distribution"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["nearest Edge Location"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "271",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "CloudFront",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "CloudFront is NOT used to deliver which of the following?",
      "answers": [
        "dynamic content",
        "static content",
        "streaming content",
        "interactive content",
        "database PUT or DELETE results"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["database PUT or DELETE results"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "272",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "CloudFront",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 4",
      "question": "CloudFront is optimized to work with which of these?",
      "answers": [
        "S3",
        "EC2",
        "ELB",
        "Route 53",
        "RDS",
        "DynamoDB"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["S3", "EC2", "ELB", "Route 53"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "273",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "CloudFront",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "CloudFront works seamlessly with Non-AWS origin servers?",
      "answers": [
        "true",
        "false"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["true"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "274",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "CloudFront",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "This type of CloudFront distribution is typically used for websites?",
      "answers": [
        "Web Distribution",
        "RTMP",
        "Streaming",
        "Static"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Web Distribution"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "275",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "CloudFront",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "This type of CloudFront distribution is typically used for media streaming?",
      "answers": [
        "Web Distribution",
        "RTMP",
        "Streaming",
        "Static"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["RTMP"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "276",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "CloudFront",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "There are over _____ Edge Locations around the world?",
      "answers": [
        "100",
        "50",
        "75",
        "1,000"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["50"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "277",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "CloudFront",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Edge Locations are not just read only; you can write to them as well (ie. put an object on them)?",
      "answers": [
        "true",
        "false"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["true"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "278",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "CloudFront",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Objects are cached in Edge Locations for the life of the _____?",
      "answers": [
        "TTL (Time to Live)",
        "TLR (Time to Rotate)",
        "TCP (Time Content Passed)",
        "TTD (Time to Die)"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["TTL (Time to Live)"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "279",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "CloudFront",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "You can clear objects out of the Edge Locations?",
      "answers": [
        "true",
        "false"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["true"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "280",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "CloudFront",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "If you explicitly clear objects from your Edge Locations cache you will NOT be charged by AWS?",
      "answers": [
        "true",
        "false"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["false"]
    }
  }
]
